const flashCardPack = [
    {
      cardId: "vouch1",
      cardQuestion: "Actual Cash Value",
      cardSolution: "In most cases it is the cost to repair or replace the damaged property, minus depreciation",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch2",
      cardQuestion: "Certificate of Insurance",
      cardSolution: "Proof of your insurance coverage",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch3",
      cardQuestion: "Deductible",
      cardSolution: "An amount the insurer will deduct from the loss before paying up to your policy limits",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch4",
      cardQuestion: "Depreciation",
      cardSolution: "The decrease in the value of property over a period of time, usually as result of age or wear and tear from use",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch5",
      cardQuestion: "Limit of Insurance",
      cardSolution: "The most that will be paid by the insurer in the event of a covered loss under an insurance policy",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch6",
      cardQuestion: "Premium",
      cardSolution: "The amount your business pays for insurance coverage",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch7",
      cardQuestion: "Replacement Value",
      cardSolution: "The cost to replace the damaged property with materials of like kind and quality, without any deduction for depreciation.",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch8",
      cardQuestion: "Rider",
      cardSolution: "This is an additional piece of coverage added onto a larger insurance policy. It may also be called an endorsement",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch9",
      cardQuestion: "Umbrella Insurance",
      cardSolution: "A policy generally written over your primary liability policy which can serve the purpose of providing coverage when the limits under your primary policy are exhausted by the payment of claims or providing coverage where the primary policy leaves off or doesnâ€™t cove",
    },
    {
      cardId: "vouch10",
      cardQuestion: "Blanket",
      cardSolution: "A single limit of insurance that applies over more than one location or more than one category of property coverage, or both",
    }
];

export default flashCardPack;
  